RG 005:035, Office of the Governor: Thomas J. Meskill (1971-1975)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 7. Agency Files, 1971-1975
  - Community Affairs Department (Box A-720)
    - Town Files (Box A-728)
      - Derby (Box A-728)
        - OEO, TEAM Grant “Headstart” (Box A-728)
        - Senior Center (Box A-728)
      - East Hartford (Box A-728)
      - East Haven (Box A-728)
      - East Windsor (Box A-728)
      - Ellington (Box A-728)
      - Enfield (Box A-729)
      - Enfield – Ind. & Business Development (IBD), 2 folders (Box A-729)
      - Fairfield (Box A-729)
      - Fairfield – Elderly Housing (Box A-729)
      - Glastonbury (Box A-729)
      - Greenwich (Box A-729)
      - Groton (Box A-729)
      - Guilford (Box A-729)
      - Hamden (Box A-729)
      - Hartford (Box A-729)
        - (General) (Box A-729)
        - CRT (Community Renewal Team) (Box A-729)
        - North End Adult Learning Center (Box A-729)
        - CRT (Community Renewal Team) Correspondence (Box A-729)
        - CRT (Help, Inc.) (Prison Rehabilitation Agency) (Box A-729)
        - Housing Rehabilitation (Box A-729)
      - Hartford Housing (Box A-729)
        - Hartford Housing Tax Abatement (Box A-729)
        - Hartford SAND (Box A-729)
      - Killingly (Box A-729)
      - Litchfield (Box A-729)
      - Mansfield (Box A-729)
      - Meriden (Box A-729)
      - Meriden – Grants (Box A-729)
      - Middletown (Box A-729)
        - Grants – OEO 10662-72/02 Community Action (Box A-729)
        - Housing (Box A-729)
        - Grants CAGM (Box A-729)
      - Milford Peter Prudden/CASEY (Box A-729)
      - Montville (Box A-729)
      - Naugatuck (Box A-729)
      - New Britain OEO (Box A-729)
      - New Britain/Spanish Speaking Center (Box A-729)
      - New Britain (Box A-729)
      - New Canaan (Box A-729)
      - New Hartford (Box A-730)
      - New Haven – Grants – LAA (Box A-730)
      - New Haven (Box A-730)
      - New Haven: (Box A-730)
        - Grants – Dixwell Legal Rts. (Box A-730)
        - Grants: CPI, CG-0115G/3 (Box A-730)
        - Coalition for Housing & Human Resources (Box A-730)
        - OIC (Opportunities Industrialization Center) (Box A-730)
        - Housing Carabetta (Box A-730)
        - Grants CPI (Box A-730)
        - Housing (Box A-730)
        - CPI (Box A-730)
        - Day Care – Elm Haven (Box A-730)
        - OEO: Dixwell Legal Rts. Assn. (Box A-730)
      - Newington (Box A-730)
      - New London (Box A-730)
      - New London – Housing (Box A-730)
      - New London – Pilot Program for Placement of Spanish American Residents (Box A-730)
      - New Milford (Box A-730)
      - Norwalk Grants (NEON) (Box A-730)
      - Norwalk (Box A-730)
      - (Box A-730)
        - Norwalk-Stamford-Danbury Regional Legal Services (Box A-730)
      - (Box A-730)
        - OEO Grant CG-1411-E/O (Box A-730)
      - Norwalk Housing (Box A-730)
      - Norwalk Housing – OEO/NSD Regional Legal Services, Inc. (Box A-730)
      - Norwich (Box A-731)
        - Harbor Improvement (R. Sharpe Arch.) (Box A-731)
        - Industrial Park (Box A-731)
      - North Canaan (Box A-731)
      - Plainfield Housing (Box A-731)
      - Plainville (Box A-731)
      - Plantsville (Box A-731)
      - Plymouth (Box A-731)
      - Portland (Box A-731)
      - Rockville Housing (Box A-731)
      - Seymour (Box A-731)
      - Shelton (Box A-731)
      - Sherman (Box A-731)
      - So. Windsor (Box A-731)
      - So. Windsor: Candlewood Apts. Heating (Box A-731)
      - Southington (Box A-731)
      - Sprague (Box A-731)
      - Stafford (Box A-731)
      - Stafford Springs (Box A-731)
      - Stamford Grants – CT & E (Box A-731)
      - Stamford Housing (Box A-731)
      - Stamford (Box A-731)
      - Stonington (Box A-731)
      - Stowe Village (Box A-731)
      - Stratford (Box A-731)
      - Thomaston (Box A-732)
      - Torrington (Box A-732)
      - Vernon (Box A-732)
      - Wallingford (Box A-732)
      - Waterbury (Box A-732)
        - Broadview Acres (Box A-732)
        - Grants (Box A-732)
        - Housing Broadview Acres (Box A-732)
        - (Waterbury) (Box A-732)
        - NOW Training Programs (Box A-732)
      - Watertown (Box A-732)
      - Westbrook (Box A-732)
      - West Hartford/Mayor Grants Puerto Ricans (Box A-732)
      - West Hartford Redevelopment (Box A-732)
      - West Haven (Box A-732)
      - Wethersfield (Box A-732)
      - Willimantic (Box A-732)
      - Winchester (Box A-732)
      - Windham Area CAP Grants WACAP (Box A-732)
      - Windham (Box A-732)
    - Grant Files by product, unarranged, 1971-1973 (Box A-733)
    - Grant Files by product, unarranged, 1971-1973 (Box A-734)
  - Comptroller’s Office (Box A-735)
    - General correspondence and monthly reports, unarranged (Box A-735)
  - Corrections Department (Box A-736)
    - General Correspondence (Box A-736)
    - Correspondence, A – J (Box A-737)
    - Correspondence, K – Z (Box A-738)
    - Subject Files (Box A-739)
      - Miscellaneous (Box A-739)
      - Adult Probation, Department of (Box A-739)
      - Annual Report, 1973 (Box A-739)
      - Appeals, Board of (Box A-739)
      - Attica (Box A-739)
      - Audit Report – Resources and Opportunities Center (Box A-739)
      - Brooklyn Site (Box A-739)
      - Capital Punishment, 4 folders (Box A-739)
      - Carrona File (Box A-739)
      - Cheshire Reformatory (Box A-739)
      - Connecticut Correctional Institute (Box A-739)
      - Cope (Box A-739)
      - Correct (Box A-739)
      - Council (Box A-739)
      - Delgado (Box A-739)
      - Correction Council (Box A-739)
      - Drug Programs (Box A-739)
      - Care of Federal Prison (Box A-739)
      - Financial Reports (Box A-739)
      - Grant, Dr. (Box A-739)
      - Guidelines (Box A-739)
      - Green, Leslie D., 2 folders (Box A-739)
      - Interdepartmental Messages (Box A-740)
      - Interfax Inc. (Box A-740)
      - Jail Site (Box A-740)
      - Legislation (Box A-740)
      - Litchfield (Box A-740)
      - Long Lane School (Box A-740)
      - Mag Card (Box A-740)
      - New Hartford Correctional Center (Box A-740)
      - New Haven Jail Site (Box A-740)
      - Pardon and Parole, Boards of (Box A-740)
      - Penal Institutions (Box A-740)
      - Perspectives (Box A-740)
      - Press Releases (Box A-740)
      - Probation and Parole (Box A-740)
      - Ombudsman Quarterly Report (Box A-740)
      - Recidivism Scroll (Box A-740)
      - Somers State Prison (Box A-740)
      - South Carolina (Box A-740)
      - Speaking Engagements, 2 folders (Box A-740)
      - Staff Meeting Minutes (Box A-740)
      - Title (Box A-740)
      - Traveling Van, Put on (Box A-740)
      - Vista Volunteers (Box A-740)
      - Volunteers (Box A-740)
      - Year End Reports (Box A-740)
  - Courts (Box A-741)
    - Correspondence A-Z, unfiled (Box A-741)
    - Subject Files (Box A-742)
      - A-C (Box A-742)
      - Calendars (Box A-742)
      - Canning (Box A-742)
      - Conelly vs. Meskill (Box A-742)
      - Danbury Courthouse (Box A-742)
      - New Haven Courthouse (Box A-742)
      - New London Courthouse (Box A-742)
      - Waterbury Courthouse (Box A-742)
      - Elks and Moose, order of (Box A-742)
      - Juvenile Court (Box A-742)
      - Juvenile Court, 2nd district (Box A-742)
      - Lituaitis (Little) (Box A-742)
      - Probate (Box A-742)
      - Property Taxes (Box A-742)
      - Court Reorganization (Box A-742)
      - Reports and Info. (Box A-742)
      - Supreme Court Issues (Box A-742)
    - Recommendations for Judge’s Appointments (Box A-743)
  - Criminal Administration Planning Committee (Box A-744)
    - Unfiled material (Box A-744)
    - Unfiled material (Box A-745)
    - Unfiled material (Box A-746)
    - Subject Files (Box A-747)
      - Audit Reports (Box A-747)
      - Bagley (Box A-747)
      - Booklet (Box A-747)
      - Command Training Institutes – Mag Card (Box A-747)
      - Communications (Box A-747)
      - Comprehensive Law – Mag Card (Box A-747)
      - Enforcement and Criminal Justices (Box A-747)
      - Executive Committee Minutes (Box A-747)
      - Executive Meetings (Box A-747)
      - Grants (Box A-747)
      - Grant Application, Copy of (Box A-747)
      - Juvenile Delinquency Youth Crime (Box A-747)
      - Lakeville Conference HR 8152 (Box A-747)
      - Law Enforcement Revenue Sharing Act of 1973 (Box A-747)
      - L.E.A.A. H.R. 8152 (Box A-747)
      - L.E.A.A. Program in Connecticut – Speech (Box A-747)
      - L.E.A.A. Programs (Box A-747)
      - Police Commissioners Association, Speech to (Box A-747)
      - Police In-Service Training Course (Box A-747)
      - Police Management – Mag letter, July, 1973 (Box A-747)
      - Speaking Engagements (Box A-747)
      - Stanton – Seiberling Amendment (Box A-747)
      - Sudden and Mysterious Deaths (Box A-747)
  - Development Commission (Box A-748)
    - General Correspondence and Publications (Box A-748)
    - Correspondence (Box A-749)
    - Subject Files (Box A-750)
      - Activities (Box A-750)
      - Annual Report, 1973 (Box A-750)
      - Arrow Hart (Box A-750)
      - Black Capitalism (Box A-750)
      - Bridgeport (Box A-750)
      - Bridgeport Waterfront Renewal (Box A-750)
      - Bristol (Box A-750)
      - Business and Industry Info., Pamphlets, etc. (Box A-750)
      - Central City, Downtown Areas and Inner-City (Box A-750)
      - Conn. Council of Economic Advisors, 1973 1st quarter (Box A-750)
      - Conn. Development Authority, 1973 November 16 (Box A-750)
      - Conn. Development News (Box A-750)
      - Conn. Vest (Box A-750)
      - Council of Economic Advisor (Box A-750)
      - Development News (Box A-750)
      - East Haven Industrial Park (Box A-750)
      - Eastern States Exposition (Box A-751)
      - Eastern States Mag, 1974 April (Box A-751)
      - Eastern States Scholarship, Governor’s (Box A-751)
      - Economic Development Administration (Box A-751)
      - Economic Development Administration – U.S. Department of Commerce (Box A-751)
      - Electric Boat Co. (Box A-751)
      - Enfield (Box A-751)
      - Etherington Commission (Box A-751)
      - Export/Import Conference (Box A-751)
      - Fantus (Box A-751)
      - Farmington Industrial Park (Box A-751)
      - First National (Box A-751)
      - General Electric (Box A-751)
      - Greater Waterbury Ambassadors (Box A-751)
      - Groton Industrial Park (Box A-751)
      - Greater Waterbury Ambassadors (Box A-751)
      - Groton Industrial Park (Box A-751)
      - Gunther Project (Box A-751)
      - Hartford Civic Center (Box A-751)
      - Hartford North Meadows Industrial Projects (Box A-751)
      - Industrial Building Commission (Box A-751)
      - Industrial Building Development (Box A-751)
      - IBD (Box A-751)
      - Legislation (Box A-751)
      - Lycoming (Box A-751)
      - Meriden Project (Box A-752)
      - Middletown Steele (Box A-752)
      - Ming, Joe (Box A-752)
      - National Federation of Independent Business (Box A-752)
      - National Homes (Box A-752)
      - Navy Underwater Systems (Box A-752)
      - Neird (Box A-752)
      - New England Council and Caucus (Box A-752)
      - New (Great) Britain (Box A-752)
      - New London Project (Box A-752)
      - New London, Retention of Underwater Systems in (Box A-752)
      - New York Hilton (Box A-752)
      - New York Reception (Box A-752)
      - New York Times (Box A-752)
      - New York Visit (Box A-752)
      - Norwich Industrial Park (Box A-752)
      - Offshore Islands and Concepts (Box A-752)
      - Press Releases (Box A-752)
      - Product Development (Box A-753)
      - Product Development Corp., 3 folders (Box A-753)
      - Regional Plan Association (Box A-753)
      - Rehab. Old Buildings (Box A-753)
      - Reverse Investment Trade Mission (Box A-753)
      - Reverse Trade Mission (Japan) (Box A-753)
      - Reverse Trade Switzerland, 1973 (Box A-753)
      - Rocky Hill (Box A-753)
      - Royal (Box A-753)
      - Sacia Conference (Box A-753)
      - Sheffield Tube (Box A-753)
      - Small Business Administration (Box A-753)
      - Smith, Tom (Box A-753)
      - Space Shuttle (Box A-753)
      - Strike Force Proposals (Box A-753)
      - Supermarine (Box A-753)
      - Tourism (Box A-753)
      - Travel Forum (Box A-753)
      - Trident Submarine Base (Box A-753)
      - United Nuclear (Box A-753)
      - Vertical (Plant Proj.), Economic Development (Box A-753)
      - Wall St. Journal Ad (Box A-753)
      - Wood stock IBD (Box A-753)
  - Education Department (Box A-754)
    - Correspondence Arranged alphabetically according to the name of sender (Box A-754)
      - A – G (Box A-754)
      - H – R (Box A-755)
      - S – Z (Box A-756)
      - Miscellaneous and unfiled material (4 files) (Box A-756)
        - 1. Education (Box A-756)
        - 2. Education (Box A-756)
        - 3. Education (Box A-756)
        - 4. Education – Information (Box A-756)
    - Subject Files (Box A-757)
      - Academic Awards - Congrats (Box A-757)
      - Academic Awards, State (Box A-757)
      - Arbitration Board (Box A-757)
      - Benhaven (Box A-757)
      - Blind, Board of Services for the, Minutes, 1973 September 20 (Box A-757)
      - Blind, Board of Education Services for the (Box A-757)
      - Board of Education, State – Report of General Assembly (Box A-757)
      - Board of Education, State – Audit Report (Box A-757)
      - Board of Education, State (Energy Crisis) (Box A-757)
      - Board of Education, State Budget Letter (Box A-757)
      - Board of Education, State (Box A-757)
      - Board of Education, State – New Members (Box A-757)
      - Board of Education, State, 1974 May 1 (Box A-757)
      - Board of Education, State, 1974 April 3 (Box A-757)
      - Board of Education, State, Minutes, 1974 May 1 (Box A-757)
      - Board of Education, State, 1974 June 5 (Box A-758)
      - Board of Education, State, Minutes of Meetings, 1974 June 5, 19 (Box A-758)
      - Board of Education, State, 1974 June 19 (Box A-758)
      - Board of Education, State, 1974 September 4 (Box A-758)
      - Board of Education, State, 1974 November 6 (Box A-758)
      - Board of Education, State, 1974 December 4 (Box A-758)
      - Board of Education, State, Meeting, 1973 March (Box A-758)
      - Board of Education, State, 1973 April 4 (Box A-758)
      - Board of Education, State, May Agenda, 1973 (Box A-758)
      - Board of Education, State, Meeting, 1973 June 6 (Box A-758)
      - Board of Education, State, 1973 July 5 (Box A-758)
      - Board of Education, State – Services for the Blind, March (Box A-758)
      - Board of Education, State – Services for the Blind, 1973 May 17 (Box A-758)
      - Board of Education, State – Suits (Tedeschi) (Box A-758)
      - Budget Letters – Education (Box A-758)
      - Budget Mag Card – Letter on A D M (Box A-758)
      - Busing, 2 folders (Box A-758)
      - Career Education (Box A-758)
      - Certificates, School, 1973 (Box A-758)
      - Certificates, Graduation, 1973-1974 (Box A-758)
      - Certificates, 1974 (Box A-758)
      - Certification of Sc. Per. (Box A-758)
      - Certification, Teacher (Box A-758)
      - Civil Defense (Box A-758)
      - Community School (Box A-758)
      - Construction Grants (Box A-758)
      - Consumer Education (Box A-758)
      - Clippings (Box A-758)
      - Deaf, American School for the (Box A-758)
      - Deaf, School for the (Box A-759)
        - Mystic Oral School (Box A-759)
        - Audit Report/Mystic Oral School (Box A-759)
      - Deaf (Box A-759)
      - Deaf and Hearing Impaired, Commission on – Mag. Card, 1974 June 19 (Box A-759)
      - Deaf – Commission to Study Hearing Impaired (Box A-759)
      - Dialogue (Box A-759)
      - Disadvantaged (Box A-759)
      - Disadvantaged Grants (Box A-759)
      - Disadvantages – Handicapped (Box A-759)
      - Dodd Memorial Library Committee (Box A-759)
      - Driver Education, 2 folders (Box A-759)
      - Early School Closing, Letter to School Superintendents on, 1971 January 8 (Box A-759)
      - Education Commission of the States, 2 folders (Box A-759)
      - Education Council, Connecticut, 2 folders (Box A-759)
      - Educational Services Center (Box A-759)
      - Educational Testing Service (Box A-759)
      - Elementary and Secondary Education Act (Box A-760)
      - Environment Education Act (Box A-760)
      - External Degrees (Box A-760)
      - Fact Sheet / Programs for Better Education (Box A-760)
      - Federal Impact Aid (Box A-760)
      - Financing, Commission to Study School (Box A-760)
      - Financing Public Schools (Box A-760)
      - Funding/Financing, School (Box A-760)
      - Food Program (Box A-760)
      - Food Programs, Special / Letters to Congress/ Reps./ Senators (Box A-760)
      - Food Program – Breakfast Program –Mag Card (Box A-760)
      - Goals Study (Box A-760)
      - Grants – ADM – Mag Card (Box A-760)
      - Grants – ADM – Mag. Card, 1974 February (Box A-760)
      - Grants – ADM and Gen. (Box A-760)
      - Grants, Education, 2 folders (Box A-760)
      - Grants to Towns, Education (Box A-760)
      - HEW (Box A-760)
      - High School Principals (Box A-760)
      - Legislation (Box A-760)
      - Legislation, 1973 (Box A-760)
      - Legislation, Federal – Pending (Box A-760)
      - Master Plan (Box A-761)
      - Migrant Workers (Box A-761)
      - NA/SBE (Box A-761)
      - NA/SBE, Board of Education and Comm. Association of (Box A-761)
      - National Reading Center (Box A-761)
      - National Youth Science Camp, 2 folders (Box A-761)
      - Needs Assessment (Box A-761)
      - NEOA (Box A-761)
      - NERCOE (Box A-761)
      - NESDEC (Box A-761)
      - NE Program in Teacher Ed. (Box A-761)
      - Non-Public School Secular Education, Advisory Council on (Box A-761)
      - [Non-Public – ] Anti-Parochial (Box A-761)
      - Non-Public, Parochial (Box A-761)
      - [Non-Public – ] St. Margaret’s School (Box A-761)
      - Nursing (Box A-761)
      - Nursing High School, 2 folders (Box A-761)
      - Nursing Task Force, 2 folders (Box A-761)
      - Partners for the Americans (Box A-761)
      - Personnel (Box A-761)
      - Press Release, CHE (Box A-761)
      - Project Concern (Box A-761)
      - Reading Assessments (Box A-762)
      - Regional and National / Travel and Part. (Box A-762)
      - Retired Teachers Association, Officers of – Mag, Card Letter Sent July 9, 1976 (Box A-762)
      - Retired Teachers – Legislation – Mag. Card Letter (Box A-762)
      - Retirement, Teachers (Box A-762)
      - Retirement, Teachers – Legislation, 2 folders (Box A-762)
      - Retirement Meeting, Teachers, March 26 (Box A-762)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box A-762)
      - Science Center (Box A-762)
      - Scholarships (Box A-762)
      - School Closing Letter (Box A-762)
      - School Closing, Printed Letter Sent in Response to Letters on (Box A-762)
      - School Prayer (Box A-762)
      - Seminar, Education (Box A-762)
      - Skill Center (Box A-762)
      - Smith Reception, 1973 July (Box A-762)
      - Special Education (Box A-762)
      - Special Revenue Sharing (Box A-762)
      - Statistics (Box A-762)
      - Strike Force Proposals for Full Employment (Box A-762)
      - Student Loans (Box A-763)
      - Student Loans – Berdun Proposal (Box A-763)
      - Student Loan Foundation (Box A-763)
      - Student Press Conference (Box A-763)
      - Telecommunications, Commission on Education and Informational Uses of Cable (Box A-763)
      - Television (Box A-763)
        - Public Television (Box A-763)
        - CPTV Show (Box A-763)
        - Connecticut Instructional TV (Box A-763)
      - Tuition A-K (Box A-763)
      - Tuition L-Z (Box A-763)
      - Tuitions (Box A-763)
      - Vocational Education (Box A-763)
        - Board of Education and Services for the Blind Board Members Manual (Box A-763)
        - Vocational/Wilcox Tech. School/Meriden (Box A-763)
        - Windham Regional Tech. (Box A-763)
        - Vocational Reclassification (Box A-763)
        - Vinal Regional Vocational Technical School (Box A-763)
        - Audit Report/Waterbury Technical College, 1974 (Box A-763)
        - Audit Report/1974/Thames Valley Technical College (Box A-763)
        - Audit/Norwalk State Technical College (Box A-763)
        - Oliver Wolcott Technical School Audits (Box A-763)
        - Windham Technical School (Box A-763)
        - Eli Whitney Technical School/Audit Reports (Box A-763)
        - Audit/E.C. Goodwin Regional Vocational (Box A-763)
        - Industrial Arts Program (Box A-763)
        - Waterbury State Technical College (Box A-763)
        - Windham Regional Vocational-Technical School -- High/Audit (Box A-764)
        - Eli Whitney Reg. Tech. (Box A-764)
        - Vocational Building (Box A-764)
        - Vocational Ed. Waterbury Case (Box A-764)
        - Enfield Vocational Tech (Box A-764)
        - Advisory Council on Vocational Education (Box A-764)
        - Vocational Education Public Hearings (Box A-764)
        - Vocational Education (Box A-764)
        - Enfield Vocational School (Box A-765)
        - Milford Vocational School (Box A-765)
        - Board of T. Reg. C. C. (Box A-765)
        - Groton Vocational Technical School (Box A-765)
        - State Colleges/Master Planning (Box A-765)
        - Branford Vocational Technical School (Box A-765)
        - Cheney Vocational School (Box A-765)
        - Warren F. Kaynor Vocational Regional Technical School (Box A-765)
        - Thames Valley State Tech. College (Box A-765)
        - Emmett O’Brien Vocational Technical School (Box A-765)
        - Platt Vocational Technical School Milford (Box A-765)
        - A. I. Prince (Box A-765)
        - Hartford State Technical College (Box A-765)
        - Hartford State Technical College/Audit (Box A-765)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation (Box A-765)
        - Norwalk State Technical College (Box A-765)
      - Voucher System (Box A-765)
      - Wallingford Board of Education (Box A-765)
  - Environmental Protection Department (Box A-766)
    - General and Unfiled material (Box A-766)
    - Correspondence (Box A-767)
      - A – G (Box A-767)
      - H – M (Box A-768)
      - N – S (Box A-769)
      - T – Z (Box A-770)
    - Subject Files (Box A-771)
      - Abandoned Cars (Box A-771)
      - Air Compliance (Box A-771)
      - Air Pollution, 2 folders (Box A-771)
      - Air Quality Plan (Box A-771)
      - Alaska Pipeline (Box A-771)
      - Ansonia Shredder (Box A-771)
      - Antoline – Mag Card (Box A-771)
      - Beaches (Box A-771)
      - Black Island (Box A-771)
      - Bluff Point (Box A-771)
      - Boat Commission – Boat Safety Act (Box A-771)
      - Bunker Boats (Box A-771)
      - Camping (Box A-771)
      - Candlewood Lake (Box A-771)
      - Candlewood Lake Authority (Box A-771)
      - Certificate of Merit (Box A-772)
      - Clean Air Commission (Box A-772)
      - Coastal Management (Box A-772)
      - Conservation and Development Plan (Box A-772)
      - Connecticut Historic Riverway (Box A-772)
      - Connecticut River Basin (Box A-772)
      - Connecticut River Basin Plan (Box A-772)
      - Connecticut River Valley Flood Control Commission (Box A-772)
      - Conservation (Box A-772)
      - Cordwood (Box A-772)
      - Cos Cob Power Plant (Box A-772)
      - Costle Appointment – Mag Card (Box A-772)
      - Costle Memorandums (Box A-772)
      - Costle Telegram Sent to Weicker and Ribicoff (Box A-772)
      - Costle Testimony (Box A-772)
      - Council on Environmental Quality, 2 folders (Box A-772)
      - Deep Water Ports (Box A-772)
      - Deer Poaching-Mag Card (Box A-772)
      - Dredging (Box A-772)
      - Education (Box A-772)
      - EEA (Box A-772)
      - Energy (Box A-772)
      - Energy Awards Given (Box A-772)
      - Energy Awards Pending (Box A-772)
      - Energy Conservation Awards (Box A-772)
      - Energy Crisis (Box A-772)